피비, 아직도야?
Are you still on hold?
2시간 전에 아빠께
전화하기로 했단 말야
I was supposed to call my dad back
two hours ago.
아까 전화하셨는데 너더러
'플림비즈'로 전화해달라셨어
Oh, yeah. He clicked on.
Call him as soon as you get a chance.
He's at Flimbees.
'플림비즈'라니?
What's Flimbees?
That's the word I use when
I can't remember the real thing.
뭔지 생각 안 날 때
쓰는 단어야
됐어, 끊어!
그만해
Okay, hang up! That's it. Come on!
No. That's what they want me to do.
안돼, 누구 좋으라고?
My warranty expires tomorrow.
If I don't get through...
보증 기간이 내일까진데
그냥 끊으면
내 전화기 무상 수리를
안 해준다구
...they won't fix my crappy,
broken phone for free!
주저앉을 수 없어
싸워서 이겨야 돼
We cannot let them win!
It's us versus them!
옳소!
Yes!
- 안녕
오늘밤 표 확인 좀 할게
어떻게 돼?
I gotta double-check for tickets
tonight. Who got what?
난 한 장!
I have one.
난 둘!
I need two. I'm bringing Pete.
난 피트랑 가
내 남자 친구!
My boyfriend.
나 남자 친구 생겼다!
I have a boyfriend now.
넌 두 장!
로스 너는?
Two it is. How about you?
Yeah, I also need two.
나도 두 장 줘
정말?
주인공이 누구야?
Really? Who's number two?
'주인공이 누구야'라...
그렇게 난감한 질문을 하다니
Whose Number Two? One of the more
difficult games sewer workers play.
No, it's just this person.
- 아직 별 사이 아냐
- 데이트하는 거야?
Like a date-type person?
Yeah, kind of.
It's this woman from work.
비슷하지만 직장동료니까
이상하게 생각하진 마
I hope that won't be too weird.
Will it, Rach?
알았지, 레이첼?
그럼, 당연하지
나도 같이 갈 사람 있어
Not at all. I was actually
gonna bring someone myself.
한 장만 달라며?
But you said one ticket.
'한 장 더' 달란 거였지
I meant me plus one.
Okay. Did you guys mean you plus one?
너희들도 '한 장 더'였어?
All right. I'll see you tonight.
- 그럼 이따 봐
- 그래
- 잘 가
- 안녕!
Okay. Bye-bye.
Bye-bye.
남자 만들어야지
Okay, I need a date!
드디어 케이트를
만나보겠구나
Oh, hey! You guys are finally
gonna get to meet Kate!
향수 좀 빌려 썼다
좋아하겠지?
And I borrowed your cologne.
I hope she likes it.
향수는 뭐하게?
케이트는 딴 사람 만난다며?
What are you doing?
She's seeing somebody.
난 향수 없는데
Yeah, and I don't have any cologne.
-Bottle next to the shaving cream.
-Worm medicine for the duck.
면도 크림 옆
녹색 병은?
오리용 벌레약 말이군
The One With the Screamer
-Here you go. You can wear this.
-Thanks.
- 자, 이거 입어
- 고마워
전화기 내려놨지만...
I'm setting the phone down.
But I'm still here.
안 끊었어요
Just don't go anywhere.
I'm still here.
안 끊었으니까
끊지 말아요
딴 데 돌리지 마요
안 끊었어요
Don't switch or anything, because
I'm right here. Just one sec.
잠깐만 기다려요
One sec. One second!
잠깐만요!
Wait! One second! Just....
기다려요!
잠깐...
- 피비
- 왜? 나 무서워
What? Monica, I'm scared!
Honey, that's a sleeve.
그건 소매잖아
And we also have a speakerphone.
그리고 스피커폰도 있고
잠시만 기다리십시오
고객의 전화는 소중합니다
Please stay on the line.
Your call is important to us.
빨리 끊어
이러다 늦겠다
You gotta hang up.
We'll be late.
오래 기다리셨습니다
바로 다음에 연결됩니다
Thank you for your patience.
You're the next caller.
됐어! 다음이래!
Yes! Yes! I'm the next caller!
끊으라고 했었니?
You were gonna have me hang up.
Can you take a duck and a chick
to the theater?
오리나 병아리가
극장에 가도 돼?
- 물론 안되지
- 안돼
Of course not.
내 말은 도무지
믿질 않아서 말야
I just wanted them to hear it
from somebody else.
루실 로텔 극장
- 레이첼!
- 왔어?
Oh, hi, how are you?
- 안녕?
- 그럼
Good.
- 우리가 제일 먼저 왔나봐
- 그런가 봐
-Looks like we're the first ones here.
-Looks that way.
1등이다!
First ones here!
이쪽은 로스
이쪽은 타미
Oh, Tommy, this is Ross.
Ross, Tommy.
이쪽은 케일린
Oh, I'm sorry. This is Cailin.
Cailin
- 안녕하세요?
- 반가워요
Sorry.
악수 끝!
And break!
- 화장 좀 고치고 올게요
- 그래요
I think I'm gonna run
to the ladies' room.
- 같이 가요
- 자리 맡아놓죠
-I'll join you.
-I'll get our seats.
이거 좀...
어색하네요
Well, this is...
...awkward.
네?
레이첼이랑 저랑
사귀던 사이잖아요
Well, because Rachel and l
used to go out.
몰랐던 사실이네요
Oh, I didn't know that.
그럼 이게 어색하네요
Well, then this is awkward.
- 자리가...
- 여기겠는데요
-So what do you...?
-I think we're here.
실례지만 여긴
저희 자리 같은데요
Excuse me. I'm sorry.
I think you may be in our seats.
아닐텐데요
No, I don't think so.
- 표 좀 볼까요?
- 그러죠
-Could we take a look at your ticket?
-Sure.
D열 13번이라고 써있는데
여긴...
Yeah. Yeah, see, this says, "D-13"....
- 전 그게...
- 그게?
Oh, well, I thought that
You thought? Well, that didn't
really work out for you. Idiot!
눈은 폼으로 달고 다녀?
멍청아!
What are you, a moron?
It says, "D-13"! Okay?
어디 모자라?
D열 13번이잖아
You're surrounded by even numbers!
Does that give you a clue?
옆자리 번호를 봐도
감이 안 와?
안내원이...
-The usher told me
-The usher must be right!
안내원은 그럴 리 없어
교육 철저히 받는다구!
With all his training!
꺼져!
Get out!
자!
Here!
- 통로 쪽에 앉을래요?
- 괜찮아요
-Hey, man, you want the aisle?
-No, I'm good.
왔구나!
-There he is!
-There's our star!
잘했어
You were great!
나 어땠어?
So? What'd you think?
시소 타는 나체 여자들
나오는 작품만큼 좋더라
Almost as good as the play with
the two naked girls on the seesaw.
- 내 출연작 아닌데
- 알아
-I wasn't in that.
-I know.
케이트, 이리 와봐
얘들아, 케이트야
I want you to meet everybody.
Everybody, this is Kate.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
Sweetheart!
실례합니다
내 사랑!
가지!
Come!
네가 좋아하는 여자야?
So that's the girl you like.
레이첼이랑 온 녀석
진짜 이상해
I tell you, this guy
Rachel is with is crazy.
He viciously screamed at total
strangers. I think he's bad news.
모르는 사람한테
악을 벅벅 쓰더라니까
질이 아주 나빠
레이첼이 만나는 남자가
싫다는 거야?
Wait a minute. You don't like
the guy Rachel's dating?
참 희한하군
Well, that's odd.
안녕, 로렌?
케이트의 대역 로렌이야
Oh, hey, Lauren. You guys, this is
Kate's understudy, Lauren.
- 반가워요
- 안녕하세요?
Hey, gosh, you look so familiar.
근데 낯이 익네요
네, 그 집 복도에서
마주쳤어요
I ran into you in the hallway
in your building.
It was right after I slept with Joey.
He dumped me the next day.
조이랑 잔 직후였는데
다음날로 절 차버렸죠
So how'd you guys meet?
어떻게 만나셨어요?
The short version is, I pursued
her for a couple of months.
짧게 말하자면
쫓아만 다니다가
2만 달러 수표로
제 사람 만들었죠
Then I gave her a check for $20,000
and she was mine.
조금 덧붙이자면,
이 얘기하다가 채이죠
In the long version, I dump him
for telling people the short version.
조이, 정말 멋졌어
Joey, sweetheart, you were fabulous!
이 분은
내 매니저 에스텔
You guys, this is my agent, Estelle.
How do you do?
반가워...
두 아가씨도 멋지던걸
Oh, you two girls were outstanding!
매니저는 있나?
Do they have representation?
- 잘못 보셨어요
- 저흰 배우 아녜요
They weren't in the play.
We're not actors.
참 아까워!
What a shame!
저 얼굴과 저 가슴이면
작품 나올 텐데
With her face and her chest,
I could really put something together.
Could I borrow it?
좀 빌릴까요?
저 안 잊었죠?
Hi. Remember me?
타미 앞에서 새치기한 사람
오늘 아주 제삿날 됐어요
Hi. Yeah. Tommy's in line
for the bathroom...
...and someone just cut.
I think he's gonna snap.
로스, 저 갈게요
I'm gonna go.
가요? 왜요?
Go? Why?
글쎄요
I don't know. Could be
because I don't feel like...
제삿날일지 아닐지도 모르는데
죽치고 기다리긴 싫어서겠죠?
...waiting all night for a guy
who may or may not scream.
케일린...
제삿날 맞다니까요
He definitely will scream.
갈게요, 로스
Goodbye.
잘 가요
여기 보세요, 여러분
Here we go, people!
'박싱 데이! '
"Boxing Day.
'루실 로텔 극장
어쩌고저쩌고... '
The Lucille Lortel Theatre....
'조이 트리비아니!
불안정한 연기를 선보였다'
Joey Tribbiani gives
an uneven performance.
'하지만 그가 최악은 아니다'
But Mr. Tribbiani is not the worst
thing in this production."
Yes!
성공이야!
'케이트 밀러의 어색한
연기는 우스꽝스럽고'
"Kate Miller's awkward and mannered
portrayal is laughable."
어쩌고저쩌고...
Here it is! "The direction...
연출자 얘기는 여기 있군
'마셜 타우넨드는...'
... by Marshall Townend is...."
Thank you, boys and girls.
고마워요, 여러분
You've ruined my life.
내 인생을 망쳐놨군요
울 엄마의 크랩 케이크를
꼴불견 낯짝에들 처바르시지
Please stuff your talentless faces...
...with my mother's crab cakes!
비켜줘요!
Excuse me!
Does anyone mind if I save this?
내가 가져도 되지?
- 피비
- 왔어?
- 연극 끝났어?
- 뭐 했어?
-ls the play over?
-Where were you?
오래 기다리셨습니다
바로 다음에 연결됩니다
Thank you for your patience.
You're the next caller.
5시간 전에도 다음이라며?
계속 듣고 있었어?
You were "the next caller" hours ago.
You must be going crazy.
나름대로 바빴지
I've kept myself busy.
네 건 쟤 방에,
쟤 건 네 방에 있어
Okay, yeah, I put your stuff in
her room and her stuff in your room.
괜찮아?
You okay?
아주 좋아
Fabulous.
Drama critics, they're nothing but
people who couldn't make it as actors.
평론가들은 자기들이 못하니까
배 아파서 그래, 근데 넌...
-You know what to do?
-Become a drama critic.
평론가나 될까?
I am hurt!
가슴 아파!
A plague...
둘 다 전염병이나 걸려라!
...on both your houses!
By the way, he dumped me tonight
after he read my review.
기사 보더니만
날 차버렸어
Oh, classy.
뻔하군!
그 수작에 놀아난 거지
I sure know how to pick them.
You know I gave up a part
on a soap for this?
이것 땜에 드라마도
포기했는데 말야
- 나도 직장 관뒀어
- 어떤 일인데?
I gave up a job too.
-Really? What?
-Declawing cats.
고양이 발톱 깎기
너희 집까지 걸어가자
Hey, tell you what,
let me walk you home.
We'll stop by every newsstand and burn
every copy of The Times and The Post.
가면서 '더 타임즈'랑
'더 포스트'를 죄다 태우자구
-Why The Post?.
-You didn't see The Post?.
- 포스트는 왜?
- 포스트 안 봤어?
응, 넌?
-No. You?
-No. Why?
나도, 왜?
날 질투해서
악평한 거라고?
You really think these newspapers
are just jealous of me?
Absolutely. You're talented
and you're good-looking.
당연하지, 넌 재능 있고
외모도 멋져
You're sweet and cute.
정말 착하고 귀여워
알아
그래서 씹힌 거잖아
I know. That's why they trashed me.
- 잠깐만!
- 왜?
-Wait. Wait a minute.
-What?
널 모르겠어
I don't get you.
처음엔 날 싫어하더니
다음엔 나랑 자고
I mean, first you hate me.
Then you sleep with me.
또 거들떠도 안 보더니
다시 날 원해?
Then you want nothing to do with me.
Now you want me again?
여배우랑 처음 데이트해?
You never went out
with an actress before?
날 좋아하긴 해?
IKate, do you even like me?
-Of course I do.
-So how come you blew me off?
물론이지
그럼 왜 날 차고
그 녀석을 만났어?
-How come you were with him?
-I don't know.
나도 몰라
나도 모르게 똑똑하고
재능 있는 사람만 찾게 돼
I just do this.
I always have to pick, like,
the smartest guy...
...or the most talented guy.
Why can't I just
pick someone like you?
너 같은 사람이면 어때서?
고마워
Thanks.
내 말 뜻 알잖아
You know what I mean.
넌 정말 따뜻해
I mean, like, the sweetest guy.
조이, 넌...
You're just so....
정말...
You're so...
...so....
그래...
눕고 발 올려야지
Here we go.
Let's get your feet up there.
잘 자, 케이트
Good night.
좋은 꿈꿔
Sweet dreams.
I'm gonna put this can right here
in case you have to hurl.
혹시 쏠리면
여기다 쏟아
잠시만 기다리십시오
고객의 전화는 소중합니다
Please stay on the line.
Your call is very important to us.
피비, 한잠도 안 잤잖아
그러다 몸 망가져
You've been up for 24 hours.
Go to sleep.
This isn't healthy.
아냐, 괜찮아
왠지 알아?
No, no, I'm fine.
리보플라빈을 먹고있거든
And you know why?
Because of all the riboflavin.
- 안녕
- 왔어?
옷이 어제랑 똑같네
Didn't you have that on last night?
응, 케이트네 갔었는데
아무 일 없었어
I stayed at Kate's
but nothing happened.
피비, 왜 안 왔어?
Hey, where were you?
정말 미안해
진짜로 가고 싶었어
I'm so, so sorry.
I am definitely gonna see your play.
I swear, your play is very important
to us. Thank you for your patience.
네 연극은 소중해
오래 기다렸구나
네 연극은
바로 다음에 봐줄게
Your play is the next play
I'm gonna see.
- 케이트하곤 어땠어?
- 정말 좋았어
How'd it go with Kate?
It was great!
집에까지 걸어갔는데
서로 통하는 느낌 있지?
I walked her home, and it was
amazing how much we connected.
기절은 하더라만...
Then she passed out.
그래도 깬 다음엔
밤새도록 얘기했어
But then she woke up.
And we stayed up all night talking.
그리고 지금은 서로
좋아서 미칠 것 같아
And now we're crazy about each other!
조이, 해냈구나
You had "the night"!
뭐?
When two people realize
their feelings for each other...
둘이 몇 시간씩 얘기하면서
서로 알아 가는 건
...and they talk for hours and learn
all about the other person.
정말 좋아한단 증거야
그럴까?
You think?
-Did you learn about her family?
-Two brothers. One died!
가족 얘기도 들었어?
- 오빠 둘 중 하난 죽었대
- 그거야!
Yes!
바에 있는 여자가 사겠대
This is from the woman at the bar.
딴 사람으로 착각했다네
Sorry. She thought
you were somebody else.
몇 시야?
-What time is it?
-One.
- 1시
7:15.
7시 15분
맛이 갔군
Watch doesn't work.
타미가 곧 올 거야
점심 먹기로 했어
Tommy's supposed to be here soon.
We're going to lunch.
이런 말 안 하려고 했는데
Look, I wasn't gonna
say anything to you, but....
All right, I don't think
you should be seeing Tommy anymore.
타미랑 안 만났음 좋겠어
그래?
You don't?
성질이 얼마나
더러운지 몰라
The guy is mean. I mean, really mean.
I think you should stay away from him.
멀리하는 게 좋겠어
남자들을 전부
멀리해야겠네?
Or maybe I should stay away
from all men.
질투심 같은 거 아냐
It's not just because I'm jealous.
정말 질투심 아냐
I mean, I'm not. I'm not jealous.
우리 자리에 잘못 앉은 부부한테
극장이 떠나가게 악을 썼다구
Look, the guy actually screamed
at this couple sitting in our seats.
그래, 연극 끝나니까
일어나서
Yeah, and at the end of the play...
...he got up, and he just started,
like, banging his hands together.
극장이 떠나가게
박수도 치더라
알았어, 안 믿는구나
다 그만둬
You don't want to believe me,
that's fine.
We're kidding.
- 농담이야
- 로스!
No one believe me.
I'm Mr. Funny to you. Mr. Funny!
아무도 안 믿다니
내가 그렇게 우스워?
- 미안해요, 타미
- 컵에 뭐 들었죠?
-Sorry, Tommy.
-What's in the cup?
컵에 뭐 들었냐구요?
What is in the cup?
Okay, it's coffee.
커피인데요
Iced coffee?
Tell me it's iced coffee.
아이스 커피요?
그렇겠죠
- 뜨거운...
- 뜨거운 커피라!
-It's hot
-Hot coffee!
이 멍청이!
뜨거운 커피를 쏟아 부어?
You idiot! You gonna spill
hot coffee all over me, huh?
What are you? Just a big, stupid
doofy idiot with a doofy idiot hairdo?
당신 뭐야? 바보 미련퉁이!
돌대가리 등신 주접쟁이!
What's your favorite thing
about summertime?
여름에 어디 가고 싶어?
늦게까지 해가 쨍쨍한
해변이 좋아
Going to the beach
when it stays light real late.
좋지
- 안녕?
- 타미...
What's your favorite thing
about summer?
여름에 뭐가 제일 좋아요?
글쎄요, 막 깎아
싱싱한 풀 냄새?
I don't know. Probably the smell
of freshly cut grass.
- 그거 멋지죠
- 맞아
That's a good one.
Sorry! Sorry I'm late! My duck and
my chick had a fight. It was ugly.
죄송해요, 오리랑 병아리가
싸우잖아요, 장난 아니었죠
잠깐 중단했어
얼른 들어가
We held the curtain for you.
Let's go!
네
빅! 어디 갔다 와?
Vic! Where have you been, baby?
- 케이트는?
- LA에 일자리 생겼대
Where's Kate?
She got a job in L.A.
뭐?
I've been waiting up all night
for you. Where have you been?
당신을 밤새 기다렸어
어디 있었어?
어디 갔다 와, 빅?
Where have you been, Vic?
창가로 가 있어
트럭에 준비해둔 게 있거든
Go to the window. I wanna run down
to the truck and show you something.
뭐가 있길래 그래, 빅?
천 밑에 뭐가 있어?
What do you got down there, Vic?
What do you got under that tarp?
- 언제 떠난대?
- 오늘밤!
When is she leaving?
Tonight. What are you doing?
뭐 하는 거야?
I'm coming up!
올라갈게
전화 좀 쓸까요?
Hey, you mind if I use the phone?
저... 그게....
잠깐만...
Use ours across the hall
because she...
건너편 우리집 가서 써요
사정이 있거든요
... has problems.
Thanks.
고마워요
미안해요, 뜨거운 커피를
쏟을 뻔했군요!
Sorry, Tommy.
I almost spilled this
hot coffee on you.
안 쏟았잖아요
Yeah, but you didn't.
아주 펄펄 끓는 건데!
No, but...
...it's hot.
로스, 제발 그만해
못 봐주겠어
Would you stop it?
It's getting really old.
- 정말 아무도 날 안 믿어?
- 난 믿어
I can't believe no one believes me.
I do. I believe you.
정말, 피비?
You do?
난 내가 다음이란
말도 믿었어
Yeah. But I also believed her
when she said I was next.
안녕?
안녕, 꼬마야?
Hey there, little fella.
복실아, 뭐 하니?
Mr. Fuzzy Man, how you doing?
더러워라!
Gross!
Idiot!
멍청이!
털복숭이 꼴통 노랭이!
Stupid, little, fuzzy, yellow creature!
짜증나고 구역질나는
병아리새끼!
"Oh, look at me! I'm so cute!
I'm a little chick who's disgusting!"
진작에 멸종이나 할 것이지!
You're so stupid!
How are you not yet extinct?
꽥꽥꽥꽥!
어디서 꽥꽥대?
What are you quacking about?
이 새대가리!
Dumb Donald Dodo!
오리한테서 떨어져!
Step away from the duck.
Sorry, little Mr. Chickadee.
미안해, 꼬마야!
누가 손에 응가하래?
Sorry you went doody in my hand!
I guess we're not going out anymore.
이쯤에서 헤어져야겠죠?
Man!
아휴!
Joey, I'm so glad I caught you.
I couldn't find you before.
- 조이!
- 케이트!
이제야 만나는구나
얼마나 찾았다구
어떻게 된 거야?
갑자기 웬 LA?
What's all this about L.A.?
They still want me
for General Hospital.
'종합 병원'에
아직 자리가 있대
But...
그럼...
우리는?
...what about us?
어젠 정말 좋았지만...
Last night was wonderful.
But I can't stay here just for you.
너 때문에
여기 남을 순 없어
그럼 박물관 일을 해
So stay for the museums.
미안해
-I'm sorry.
-Joey, on-stage!
조이, 올라가!
At least stay till the end
of the play.
끝날 때까지 기다려 줘
공항까지 배웅할게
I'll go to the airport with you.
I want to say goodbye.
- 작별인사는 해야지
- 어디 있어, 빅?
Where are you, Vic?
Flight's in an hour.
I gotta go.
비행기 시간 땜에 안돼
빅?
Vic?
-Vic!
-ln a minute!
- 빅!
- 금방 갈게!
이걸로 끝이야, 빅?
So this is it, Victor?
그래, 그럴 거야
Yeah. I guess it is.
작별인사 할게
Listen...
... I gotta say goodbye, and I gotta say
it quick because this is killing me.
그래, 마음 아프니까
빨리 해치울래
이것만은 명심해
당신을 절대 안 잊어
One thing you gotta know
is that I will never forget you.
But you got things
you have to do now.
당신도 할 일이 있고
나도 마찬가지잖아
And so do l.
그럼 이제...
And so...
우주선에 올라도 되겠지?
... I'm gonna get on
this spaceship...
블라곤 7호 행성에
대체 연료를 찾으러 가
...and I'm gonna go to Blaargon-7
in search of alternative fuels.
갔다오면...
2백 년 후엔
But when I return
200 years from now...
당신은 가고 없겠지
...you'll be long gone...
난 그대로겠지만
... but I won't have aged at all.
내 증손녀의 증손녀한테
날 찾으라고 전해 줘
So you tell your great,
great granddaughter...
...to look me up.
에이드리안, 왜냐하면...
Because, Adrianne...
자기!
... baby...
그 애가 보고싶을 거거든
... I'm gonna want to meet her.
안녕, 빅!
So long, Vic!
It's been two days.
피비, 벌써 이틀째야
Yeah, I know.
알아
Good thing it's one of those
801 numbers, right?
그나마 801전화니까
다행이잖아?
피비, 800이 무료전화고
801은 유타야
Phoebe, 800 is toll free.
801 is Utah.
It has to be 800 because all those
big companies have 800 numbers.
아냐, 잘못 안 거야
큰 회사는 다
801전화가 있어
Every....
유타에 있는
큰 회사가 그렇구나
Yeah, every big Utah-based company
has one.
피비!
Sorry. I'm so sorry.
I will pay you back.
미안해, 전화요금 줄게
근데 아직도 전화를
안 끊고 있어
And yet she's still not
hanging up the phone.
- 끊어!
- 빨리 끊어!
-Hang up!
-Hang up the phone!
Fine! Fine!
알았어!
뭐야?
Well, I think I broke it.
깨진 것 같은데
걱정 마
여기다 전화하면 돼
But that's all right.
Here's the number where you can call.